http://www.batteryuniverse.com/help/privacy

Privacy Policy
At battery-universe.com, we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy, so we've instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. We also have posted this privacy policy to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled, what choices you have regarding our use of your information, and how you may access some of the data you provide to us.
As we continue to develop our Web site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this policy likely will change. We therefore encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.
If you have any questions about this policy, you can contact us at 208-347-2744.
Be assured that we will never sell or share your information with any organization, with the exception of businesses related to the processing of your order (ex. UPS, Fedex, USPS, third-party suppliers).
Unless you request, we do not store credit card information.
With the problems with recent security breaches around the world, we felt it best to destroy that information after the order is processed. You may request that we keep your credit card data on file if you place orders on a regular basis.
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect various types of information depending upon how you use our site.
When you order from us, we collect your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit card number (with expiration date) or gift card number. We also gather information on the person who will receive any gift you send (e.g., that person's name and address) and we will retain a record of your purchases.
When you become a battery-universe.com registered user, we collect your name, mailing address, email address, birth date, password, and password clue (in case you forget your password). This information is gathered to make your shopping experience as a registered user the quickest, and easiest possible.
We also gather information on the person who will receive any gift you send (e.g., that person's name and address) and we will retain a record of your purchases. If you are a registered user and have signed in when you enter this information, it is automatically saved in your Address Book for your ease of reference.
At Checkout, we collect the above information, as well as a credit card number and a billing and shipping address. If you are a registered user and have signed in before entering that information, it will be automatically saved in your Wallet.
When you submit a question to customer service, we need your email address to respond, and you also may provide us with various additional information to help us answer your question.
We also may receive some information about you from other sources and may add it to your account information. For example, we might get your updated address from a shipper or information on your preferences from another Web site conducting a promotion or event with us.
What Are Cookies and Do We Use Them?
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a Web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to interact with you and personalize your experience. At battery-universe.com, we use two kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies.
Session cookies exist only for as long as your browser remains open. Once you exit your browser, they go away. We use session cookies to maintain information we need to have in order for you to shop at battery-universe.com. For example, the Session ID cookie that we ask your browser to hold retains the ID for your shopping bag. Without the Session ID cookie, you can't add merchandise to your bag and carry it to Checkout.
Persistent cookies, in contrast, last from visit to visit; they do not go away when you exit your browser. At battery-universe.com, we are preparing to use persistent cookies to give you a more personalized shopping experience and to help you navigate our store more efficiently. We will use your information to enhance your site experience. However, you can use our site without accepting a persistent cookie. To do so, you should set your browser options to reject persistent cookies. Alternatively, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which gives you the opportunity to decide whether you want to accept it or not. In many instances, the Help button on your browser toolbar will tell you how you can take these steps.
Cookies can be used by a Web site to recognize you. But that does not necessarily mean any personal information is stored in the cookies. At battery-universe.com, we store no personal information about you in the cookies. Anything you choose to tell us about yourself (such as your address and email address) is stored safely and separately on our secured servers, and you need to provide a password to access it.
We also use cookies to look at how groups, rather than individuals, use our Web site. In our physical stores, we can observe which aisles and departments are most heavily trafficked and determine what displays or sales are the most successful. Then, we can identify ways to improve the customer experience. On the Web, cookies help us develop a similar understanding so that we can continue to improve the arrangement, product offerings, and merchandise placement you see at battery-universe.com.
How Do We Use Your Information?
We may use your information in a number of ways, including the following:
To improve the content on our Web site. For example, we may use cookies to find out which parts of our site or our products are visited most often.
To enhance your online shopping experience. For example, we may use it to recognize you and welcome you to the site.
For marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we send out emails to our customers about products or events that we think may be of interest to them. We also may send you offers for discounts or free services (e.g., free gift wrap or shipping) on our site.
Additionally, battery-universe.com may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law or to our protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection.
And in the event that some or all of the business assets of battery-universe.com are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information about our customers.
Customer Testimonials
Specials
Bullard T3, T3MAX Battery$54.95BT-023436-001 Radio Battery$83.95Motorola APX 4000 Battery$67.95
At Battery Universe we accept payment with most major credit cards include MasterCard, VISA, American Express and Discover
Pay with PayPal
Most orders ship via UPS
© Copyright 2020 Battery Universe
All Rights Reserved.
Battery Universe
and the Battery Universe Name and Company logo are trademarks of Battery Universe and/or its affiliates in
the U.S. and other countries where applicable. All other trademarks mentioned throughout this web site and logos
displayed are the property of their respective owners.
